Katrina Kuan Su Yin

Email: katrinakuansy@gmail.com | Mobile: (+65) 8157 3656

City : Singapore

Date of Birth: 4th December 1991

Nationality: Malaysian (Singapore PR)



Profile

Currently holding a 2nd year senior audit associate position with an extensive 4 years external audit experience in major accounting firms. Audit portfolio includes banking industries, asset & fund management, private and publicly held manufacturing companies. Exposed and highly keen on consultancy in market dealings & communications in a professional environment. Excellent communicator who speaks fluent English, Malay, Chinese and Cantonese. Possesses strong team leadership, project team management, and multi-tasking skills. Technically proficient in Microsoft Office and data analytical skills. Enjoys communicating and developing new ideas. Keen to enhance self-growth with more learning opportunities in a new environment and adaptable to challenges with a positive attitude. Independent and work well under pressure.

Work Experience

KPMG, Singapore (2014 to present)

Senior Audit Associate

- 4 years of audit experience in reputable banks, asset management companies and listed manufacturing companies.
- 6 months experience in Forensic Accounting projects with project management roles.
- Experience and handled compliance audit for regulatory reporting for CMSL license holders, anti-money laundering and regulatory submissions.
- Team leader for monitoring audit team for regulatory reporting for banks and listed manufacturing companies.
- Exposed to project budgeting and cost management.
- Exposed to monitoring of internal controls and data analysis using provided software.
- Extensive knowledge on credit review for loans provided by banks
- Facilitated good communication with internal auditors and component auditors in a different country to complete project within stipulated timeline.
- Provided guidance and advices for preparation of annual financial statements.
- Project team leader for special projects such as the "Enterprise 50 Award Program" which includes data compilation and analysis for awarding small-medium enterprises (SME).

Ernst & Young, EY, Malaysia (2013 to 2014)

Audit Associate

- Audit experience in audit of commercial banks and investment banks
- Exposed to loans credit review, money market funds, treasury, investments & asset management
- Performed analytical review and strategies on financial reports accordingly
- Assisted in accounts reconciliation and preparation of financial statements for financial year end

Alcatel-Lucent Malaysia Sdn Bhd (2011 – 2012)

Intern

- Assisted in accounts receivable and payable team in Finance Department
- Worked closely with Chief Financial Officer to assist in financial reporting and reconciliation of accounts
- Fully utilized the usage of SAP accounting software

UCSI University, Malaysia (2009 – 2013)

Student Council

- Student council for National Marketing Department
- Team lead and support in publicity and organizing education fairs held in various venues
- Provided administrative support to Head of Marketing

EDUCATION

CPA, Australia (2014 – 2017)

• Completed

UCSI University, Malaysia (2009 - 2013)

- Bachelor of Arts (Hons) in Accounting with Second Upper Class with Honors
- CGPA: 3.35 out of 4.00

Kolej Tunku Abdul Rahman, Malaysia (2009)

- Cambridge A-Levels (Science)
- Merit Scholarship from Tar College

Secondary High School, Malaysia

- Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (Equivalent to GCE 'O' Level), 2008
- Results: 4 High Distinctions (HD), 6 Distinctions (D)

ACHIEVEMENT

- UCSI Scholarship Award (2008)
- Sijil Yayasan Pendidikan Cheras (YPC) Excellent Achiever Award SPM 2008
- Full merit scholarship in Cambridge A Levels (Science) (2009)
- Hip-hop Street Dance Award (2006)

CLUBS & ACTIVITIES

KPMG ISCA Games Badminton representative (October 2015)

EY Inter-Department Games (IDFG) Badminton representative (July 2014)

UCSI Dance Club Active participant (September 2012)

SMKSBU Librarian Board Head of Committee & Department (2008)

SMKSBU Chinese Society Club Head of Committee (2008)

SMKSBU Judo Society Head of Committee (2008)

REFEREE

Name : Melvin Tan
Position : Senior Manager
Employer : KPMG, Singapore
Contact : +65 9027 5549

Name : Tee G-Mun
Position : Manager
Employer : EY, Malaysia
Contact : +60 12 938 6681